<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OpenGLBase</string>
    <string name="app_title">Droidcon Berlin 2024</string>
    <string name="session_title">Building a native AR app with Compose &amp; OpenGL ES</string>
    <string name="project_description">This project showcases how to integrate OpenGL ES rendering with Jetpack Compose. The different samples go from more basic to more complex integrating ARCore.\n\n\nThis project has been created by Pau Guillamon for the Droidcon Berlin 2024 conference.</string>
    <string name="arcore_dependency_explanation">This project requires ARCore to be installed and up to date. If your device is not supported by ARCore, some samples won\'t work.</string>
    <string name="arcore_install_button">Install ARCore</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>

    <string name="sample1_description">Basic implementation showcasing one possible way of integrating a GLSurfaceView within Compose.</string>
    <string name="sample2_description">Extends Sample1 by showcasing how multiple GL views can be used and applies different clipping to them.</string>
    <string name="sample3_description">Showcases a very basic "rendering" engine that shows a single rotating cube with a texture.</string>
    <string name="sample4_description">This sample integreates howing the camera feed from ARCore. There is a rotating cube floating as an overlay but it is not an Augmented Reality experience.</string>
    <string name="sample5_description">Full sample integrating ARCore and placing more cubes in the real world. The cubes are occluded when they appear behind a real world object.</string>
    <string name="sample5_fps">FPS: %1s</string>
    <string name="sample5_toggle_feature_points">Feature points</string>
    <string name="sample5_toggle_depth_map">Depth Map</string>
    <string name="sample5_toggle_eis">EIS</string>
    <string name="sample5_delete_last">Delete last</string>

    <string name="camera_permission_rationale">Without the camera permission, this project cannot execute the AR experience.</string>
    <string name="camera_permission_please_grant">Camera permission is needed to run this project. Please, grant the permission in settings.</string>
    <string name="camera_request_permission">Request camera permission</string>
</resources>